Guide to the Brown & Root / George R. Brown Executive Files, 1937-1978 MS 488
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Brown Shipbuilding Company Files, 1939-1950; (3 linear ft., 5 boxes)
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence, 1946-1950
    Carbon copies and some original items such as internal memos and external correspondence, between Brown Shipbuilding and law firms, accountants, and insurance firms, relating to the release of contracts, labor issues, and inventory.
    - 1946 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - 1947 (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
    - 1948 (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
    - 1949-50 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Gro-Gy (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence Leo-Lim (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Houston Corporation, 1946-1947 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: Law suits
    - R.E. Hale et.al. suit, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Houston Natural Gas Corp. suit, 1946-1947 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - George H. Hill et al. suit, 1940s (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - J.H. Howard P.M. Culbreth v. Herman George Brown, 1947-1948 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: Photographs
    - Events (Box 44, Folder 9-11)
    - Events (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Individuals and groups (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
    - Interior views of PC-1253, March 30, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - George Brown/Herman Brown - individually and with groups (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: Award certificates and ephemera
    - Payroll Savings Plan Official Commendation, c. 1939 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Harris County Community Chest and Council Certificate of Merit, 1944, for Shipping Dept. and Tank Testing Dept. (2) (Box 46)
    - Harris County Community Chest and Council Certificate of Merit, 1944, for Shipping Dept. and Tank Testing Dept. (2) (Box 46)
    - "E" flag and photo (Box 46)